>> Then you open correctly.
>> But you uh do you have a party trick then you
who is out on the swing so much?
>> Yes, I put snuff in the forecourt.
>> No, exactly that. But it's for the hell of it
the forest. Yes, that's just the way it is. Dear child
have many
>> dudes.
>> No.
>> dear child. How many friends?
No. Dear child has many names.
>> I have now heard it, I think actually
was at school like it was supposed to
>> Yes yes yes yes. Do you understand? Yes.
>> Mmm. Neat.
>> What you don't have in your head, you have to have in it
>> the butt.
>> Yes it No it is not No no no no.
in the legs.
>> What you don't have
>> what you don't have in your head, you have to have in it
the legs.
>> That means if, for example, you uh go
away from home and you forget to uh and close
of the coffee brewer,
>> then you can run home.
>> Yes, please, someone. I am I am very
glad you fixed it.
>> Yes, of course.
>> If you want to be nice, you have to suffer
>> pins?
>> pain?
>> Thank you. Money doesn't grow
>> tree.